<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>GMUN</title><link>https://genmun.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on GMUN</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://genmun.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Team</title><link>https://genmun.github.io/team/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 11:40:12 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://genmun.github.io/team/</guid><description>Secretary General Kolej GENIUS@pintar Muhammad Syarif bin Mohd Shariful Azwan Deputy Secretary General Kolej GENIUS@pintar Wan Muhammad Daniel bin Wan Junaidi Secretary Kolej GENIUS@pintar Aqil Ar-Rayyan bin Muhammad Haniff Deputy Secretary Kolej GENIUS@pintar Amelia Siow Treasurer Kolej GENIUS@pintar Muhammad Anas bin Zamri Deputy Treasurer Kolej GENIUS@pintar Choong Cheng Ken Accommodation Head of Committee Kolej GENIUS@pintar Nur Qistina Ardinie binti Muhammad Shahrir Committee members:
Asphela Jicue Anak Quat (ASpi) Dalili Syahmina Binti Mahadi Dinie Khalis bin Zamzul Hisham (ASpi) Khaira Adriana binti Nor Azizi Muhammad Ikhlas bin Mohd Faizal Nimexsionre Sulani Nur Aliah Atikah Bt Tumiran Nurul Iman binti Mohamad Awards Head of Committee Kolej GENIUS@pintar Xinicky Madel Committee members:</description></item><item><title>About Us</title><link>https://genmun.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 20:16:59 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://genmun.github.io/about/</guid><description>What is MUN? The Model United Nations, usually known as MUN, is an academic simulation of the meetings and discussions held by the councils at the United Nations (UN). In an MUN, students ranging from high school to tertiary education, are exposed to diplomacy skills, international relations, real-world issues, and the UN, as a whole.
Students participating in an MUN conference take up the role of a nation&amp;rsquo;s delegate to the UN where they partake in fruitful discussions about real-world issues.</description></item><item><title>Venue</title><link>https://genmun.github.io/venue/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 12:15:10 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://genmun.github.io/venue/</guid><description>How to get here By Car Pusat GENIUS@Pintar Negara,
Universiti Kebangsaan Malaysia,
43600 Bangi,
Selangor,
Malaysia
google map in wordpress By Public Transport MRT Sungai Buloh-Kajang Line
Nearest station: Kajang Line Frequency: 10 minutes Price: around MYR 4.00 Komuter Seremban Line
Nearest station: UKM Line Frequency: 30 minutes - 1 hour Price: around MYR 5.00 E-hailing service
Popular provider: Grab, AirAsia Price: around MYR 15.00 from station to our center Once you arrive at Kajang MRT station or UKM Komuter station, we highly recommend taking e-hailing service to our center since it is considerably faster and less hassle.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://genmun.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 11:40:44 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://genmun.github.io/contact/</guid><description>If you have any questions or inquiries, please do not hesitate to reach out to us directly at info@gmun.my. We look forward to hearing from you!
Alternatively, you can message us at one of our social media linked at the bottom of the page. Our team works around the clock to make sure that you receive your reply as soon as possible.
Need to mail us something? You can do so here:</description></item><item><title>Registration</title><link>https://genmun.github.io/registration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 22:28:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://genmun.github.io/registration/</guid><description>Registration for GMUN 2023 has not yet opened
Registration Prices and Info Package Information Price Deadline Group Registration includes access to all conference events MYR 600 TBA Accommodation (optional) includes overnight stay at our official accommodation TBA TBA Chair Application (optional) delegate may apply to participate as chair None TBA To register as a delegation/group, have your head delegate or faculty advisor fill out the group registration form. The registration fee for a group consisting of five delegates and one head advisor is set at MYR 600.</description></item><item><title>Frequently Asked Questions</title><link>https://genmun.github.io/faq/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 16:33:54 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://genmun.github.io/faq/</guid><description>General Information What is GMUN? Is this the same conference/organization as PERMUN? What is Model United Nations (MUN)? When is GMUN 2023? Where is GMUN 2023? What are the objectives of GMUN 2023? What language is used at GMUN 2023? What is the theme of GMUN 2023? Registration How do I register to attend? What are the fees and what do they cover? Who are eligible to participate? Is accommodation provided?</description></item><item><title>Schedule</title><link>https://genmun.github.io/schedule/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://genmun.github.io/schedule/</guid><description>*Schedule is Subject to Change 16 June 2023 Friday Time Activity 1:30pm - 3:30pm Registration 3:45pm - 5:00pm Opening Ceremony 5:00pm - 5:30pm Press Conference 5:30pm - 7:00pm Council Session 1 7:00pm - 8:30pm Dinner 8:30pm Dismissal 17 June 2023 Saturday Time Activity 8:00am - 8:30am Breakfast 8:30am - 12:30pm Council Session 2 1:00pm Lunch 3:00pm - 6:30pm Council Session 3 8:00pm - 10:00pm Social Night 10:15pm Dismissal 18 June 2023 Sunday Time Activity 8:00am - 8:30am Breakfast 8:30am - 12:30pm Council Session 4 12:30pm Lunch 2:30pm - 4:30pm Awards Ceremony 4:30pm Goodbye</description></item></channel></rss>