<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>GMUN</title><link>https://gmun.my/</link><description>Recent content on GMUN</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gmun.my/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Materials</title><link>https://gmun.my/materials/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 12:14:34 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://gmun.my/materials/</guid><description>Rules of Procedure The GMUN conference will always use the most updated set of HMUN Rules of Procedure. Click on the link below to get more information regarding Rules of Procedure of HMUN.
HMUN Rules of Procedure</description></item><item><title>Accommodation</title><link>https://gmun.my/team/accommodation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gmun.my/team/accommodation/</guid><description> Head of Accommodation Committee Nur Qistina Ardinie binti Muhammad Shahrir Committee Members Asphela Jicue Anak Quat Dalili Syahmina Binti Mahadi Dinie Khalis bin Zamzul Hisham Khaira Adriana binti Nor Azizi Muhammad Ikhlas bin Mohd Faizal Nimexsionre Sulani Nur Aliah Atikah Bt Tumiran Nurul Iman binti Mohamad</description></item><item><title>Awards</title><link>https://gmun.my/team/awards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gmun.my/team/awards/</guid><description> Head of Awards Committee Xinicky Madel Committee Members Amilah Fadhlina Iman Nuaiyman bin Nor Azmi Nea Sarra binti Mohd Suhaimi Nur Arleesya Arween Binti Azman Raihana Khaisara Binti Khairul Fitri Wan Muhamad Harith bin Wan Mohd Noor</description></item><item><title>Food</title><link>https://gmun.my/team/food/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gmun.my/team/food/</guid><description> Head of Food Committee Aina Batrisyia binti Mohd Rafee Head of Food Committee Sarah Diyanah binti Yusnizam Committee Members Ahla binti Mahadi Auni Nabilah Hasif Arfan Bin Shamsul Joesyazwana binti Juhari Jonathan Soh Lee Chen Muhammad Muqharabbin bin Muhammad Zulkarami</description></item><item><title>Multimedia</title><link>https://gmun.my/team/multimedia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gmun.my/team/multimedia/</guid><description> Head of Multimedia Committee Emir Hakim bin Suhaimi Head of Multimedia Committee Jack Lim Wei Jye Head of Multimedia Committee Qistina Aisyah binti Abdul Razak Committee Members Alyssa Iris Wafeeya binti Zikrilwafeer Amira Aisha Razman Aqil Mukhlis bin Rosman Carlisha Mia binti Khairul Anwar Chew Xin Ying Daveena Ashwini Dhana Raj Dinie Khalis bin Zamzul Hisham Khaira Adriana binti Nor Azizi Muhammad Aiman Syafiq bin Mohd Hanafi Nas Nadine Nabeeha binti Nasrudin Nur Irdina Safiya Nur Syifaa&amp;rsquo;Raihanah Binti Suffian Hadi Nurdini Hannah binti Mohammad Nazren Qawiemah Batrisyia binti Syaiful Izzat Sarah Zahirah binti Ahmad Zakri</description></item><item><title>Performance</title><link>https://gmun.my/team/performance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gmun.my/team/performance/</guid><description> Head of Performance Committee Nur Emysha Rina binti Abd Aziz Committee Members Khaira binti Khalid Nur Zeti Ashikin binti Shamsul Bahari</description></item><item><title>Protocol and Technical</title><link>https://gmun.my/team/protocalandtechnical/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gmun.my/team/protocalandtechnical/</guid><description> Head of Protocol and Technical Committee Ling Chin Wei Head of Protocol and Technical Committee Nur Alya Maisarah binti Erno Zan Committee Members Aimi Nur Hikmah binti Norhasyimi Nur Iman Insyirah binti Shaifulsahrizan Pavitra Suresh Kumar Tun Muhammad Anas bin Aris</description></item><item><title>Registraton</title><link>https://gmun.my/team/registration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gmun.my/team/registration/</guid><description> Head of Registration Committee Amelia Adam Cheah Head of Registration Committee Haziqah Natrah binti Wahab Committee Members Danial Haziq Bin Asnizan Kirtana Saralin A/P Noel Devan Leia Mayssa binti Masyerin Lew Jia Jin Logan A/L Kannan Muhammad Akmal Hadi bin Md Shukri Ng Yi Teng Nur Husna Aisyah Nurul Nabila Tan Rou Bei</description></item><item><title>Secretariat</title><link>https://gmun.my/team/secretariat/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gmun.my/team/secretariat/</guid><description> Secretary General Muhammad Syarif bin Mohd Shariful Azwan Deputy Secretary General Wan Muhammad Daniel bin Wan Junaidi Secretary Aqil Ar-Rayyan bin Muhammad Haniff Deputy Secretary Amelia Siow Treasurer Muhammad Anas bin Zamri Deputy Treasurer Choong Cheng Ken</description></item><item><title>Social Night</title><link>https://gmun.my/team/socialnight/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gmun.my/team/socialnight/</guid><description> Head of Social Night Committee Angelyn Liaw Yee Ern Head of Social Night Committee Nurul Iman binti Tajulmar Committee Members Aliyah Chioma Amirah Annel Binti Abdullah Amirul Hakimi Arianna Qistina Binti Mohd Saharudi Asphela Jicue Anak Quat Batrisyia binti Mohamad Lau Tze Shuen Leow Zi Rong Nas Nadine Nabeeha binti Nasrudin Nasreen Qasrina binti Nasry Nur Eliesa Farisha binti Suwito Nur Husna Huzaifah Binti Abdul Rahman Shassvinn Rajamanickam Siti Iman Nasuha binti Shafie Vagesh A/L Kumaran Wong Jen Nam Yeoh Sing Ching</description></item><item><title>Venue</title><link>https://gmun.my/venue/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gmun.my/venue/</guid><description>About Our Center As part of the GENIUS@pintar education programme, the school provides gifted Malaysian students with a focused and holistic learning environment. It is no surprise that The PERMATApintar　（now known as GENIUS@pintar) Auditorium and Sports Park, designed by GDP architects, have won multiple awards such as 2015 PAM Awards, the premier award for architecture in Malaysia. The park includes an auditorium, running track, football field, Olympic-sized swimming pool and spectator facilities.</description></item><item><title>Volunteering</title><link>https://gmun.my/team/volunteering/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gmun.my/team/volunteering/</guid><description> Head of Volunteering Committee Adam Haidhar bin Hassan Head of Volunteering Committee Muhammad Farihin bin Ruslan Committee Members Ahmad Khayr Bin Zolkifle Ahmad Nabil bin Abidin Airell Ikhwan Bin Adnan Alya Rifhan Binti Azman Amirah Annel Binti Abdullah Ar Rayyan bin Muhammad Zubaidi Auni Syafiah binti Azahari Carlisha Mia binti Khairul Anwar Chen Zi Xian Chloe Tan Hui Xin Daneea Mysara Binti Junaidi Danial Haziq Bin Asnizan Lau Tze Shuen Leow Zi Rong Muhammad Arif Shaikhan Bin Ahmad Muhammad Ismarazi bin Ismail Muqhlisa Natasha Binti Muhammad Nizam Muqri Danish bin Mazri Nimexsionre Sulani Nur Haziqah Fatin Binti Hanafee Nur Irdina Safiya Nursyasya Qasrina binti Mohd Syahiran Nurul Iman binti Mohamad Pavitra Suresh Kumar Poi Shie Chee Sachien A/L Siva Sarah Zahirah binti Ahmad Zakri Shassvinn Rajamanickam Tengku Nurina Athirah binti Tengku Ahmad Nawab Vagesh A/L Kumaran</description></item><item><title>About Us</title><link>https://gmun.my/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gmun.my/about/</guid><description>What is MUN? The Model United Nations, usually known as MUN, is a simulation of actual United Nations conferences. Participants are known as delegates, and are each assigned a country to represent as well as a council or committee to participate in. Throughout the conference period, delegates will have to discuss a given topic and reach a resolution with the rest of their council members by the end.
About GMUN GENIUS Model United Nations 2023 (GMUN 2023) is a Model United Nations Conference held by our school, Kolej GENIUS@Pintar Negara and ASASIpintar UKM.</description></item><item><title>Councils</title><link>https://gmun.my/councils/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gmun.my/councils/</guid><description>Note: The topics for GMUN 2023 have not been announced yet. Once updated, all topics, chairs and countries will be available on this page.
GMUN 2023 will be using HMUN Rules of Procedure. Please check out the materials page for more details.
Beginner Councils UNEP United Nations Environment Programme WHO World Health Organization DISEC Disarmament and International Security Committee UNWOMEN United Nations Women Intermediate Councils ECOSOC Economic and Social Council UNDP United Nations Development Programme ASEAN Association of Southeast Asian Nations Advanced Councils Crisis Crisis Council WTO World Trade Organization Special Council Press Press Corps</description></item><item><title>Frequently Asked Questions</title><link>https://gmun.my/faq/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gmun.my/faq/</guid><description>General Information What is GMUN? Is this the same conference/organization as PERMUN? What is Model United Nations (MUN)? When is GMUN 2023? Where is GMUN 2023? What are the objectives of GMUN 2023? What language is used at GMUN 2023? What is the theme of GMUN 2023? Registration How do I register to attend? What are the fees and what do they cover? Who are eligible to participate? Is accommodation provided?</description></item><item><title>Schedule</title><link>https://gmun.my/schedule/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gmun.my/schedule/</guid><description>*Schedule is Subject to Change 16 June 2023 Friday Time Activity 1:30pm - 3:30pm Registration 3:45pm - 5:00pm Opening Ceremony 5:00pm - 5:30pm Press Conference 5:30pm - 7:00pm Council Session 1 7:00pm - 8:30pm Dinner 8:30pm Dismissal 17 June 2023 Saturday Time Activity 8:00am - 8:30am Breakfast 8:30am - 12:30pm Council Session 2 1:00pm Lunch 3:00pm - 6:30pm Council Session 3 8:00pm - 10:00pm Social Night 10:15pm Dismissal 18 June 2023 Sunday Time Activity 8:00am - 8:30am Breakfast 8:30am - 12:30pm Council Session 4 12:30pm Lunch 2:30pm - 4:30pm Awards Ceremony 4:30pm Goodbye</description></item><item><title>Team</title><link>https://gmun.my/oldteam/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 11:40:12 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://gmun.my/oldteam/</guid><description>Secretary General GMUN 2023 Muhammad Syarif bin Mohd Shariful Azwan Deputy Secretary General GMUN 2023 Wan Muhammad Daniel bin Wan Junaidi Secretary GMUN 2023 Aqil Ar-Rayyan bin Muhammad Haniff Deputy Secretary GMUN 2023 Amelia Siow Treasurer GMUN 2023 Muhammad Anas bin Zamri Deputy Treasurer GMUN 2023 Choong Cheng Ken Accommodation Head of Committee Accommodation Nur Qistina Ardinie binti Muhammad Shahrir Committee members:
Asphela Jicue Anak Quat (ASpi) Dalili Syahmina Binti Mahadi Dinie Khalis bin Zamzul Hisham (ASpi) Khaira Adriana binti Nor Azizi Muhammad Ikhlas bin Mohd Faizal Nimexsionre Sulani Nur Aliah Atikah Bt Tumiran Nurul Iman binti Mohamad Awards Head of Committee Awards Xinicky Madel Committee members:</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://gmun.my/contact/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 11:40:44 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://gmun.my/contact/</guid><description>If you have any questions or inquiries, please do not hesitate to reach out to us directly at genmodelun@gmail.com. We look forward to hearing from you!
Alternatively, you can message us at one of our social media linked at the bottom of the page. Our team works around the clock to make sure that you receive your reply as soon as possible.
Need to mail us something? You can do so here:</description></item><item><title>Registration</title><link>https://gmun.my/registration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 22:28:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://gmun.my/registration/</guid><description>Registration for GMUN 2023 has not yet opened
GROUP REGISTRATION Eligibility GMUN 2023 is open to students who are:
Of any nationality or citizenship Of any gender, race, or ethnicity Currently enrolled in any educational institution of any level Registration Instructions Step 1: Fill in the Registration Form Students interested in applying to the conference may apply through a school or as an individual delegate.
As such, applicants may apply through two different channels:</description></item></channel></rss>